https://firsthome.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We are committed to protecting the privacy of our clients. We want you to know the type of information collected and how it is used.
First Home Mortgage Corporation does not share or sell your personal information with outside companies for their promotional use. Please see the information below for a full explanation of how we collect, use and protect your personal information.
FACTS
WHAT DOES FIRST HOME MORTGAGE CORPORATION DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number And Credit ScoreAccount Balances and Payment HistoryIncome and Employment Information
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons FIRST HOME MORTGAGE CORPORATION chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Questions? Call 877-933-3100 or go to www.firsthome.com
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?
FIRST HOME MORTGAGE CORPORATION
What we do
How does FIRST HOME MORTGAGE CORPORATION protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does FIRST HOME MORTGAGE CORPORATION collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
Apply for a loan or provide account information.Provide contact information.Provide your income, employment and/or asset information.
OR
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes – information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
First Home Mortgage Corporation has no affiliates
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. First Home Mortgage Corporation does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
First Home Mortgage Corporation does not jointly market
Connect With Us
Contact Us
For security purposes, please do not disclose any confidential or sensitive information.
To speak with a loan officer, please see
Find a Loan Officer.
For servicing questions, please call
443-725-8938 ext. 1008
(877) 933-3100
5355 Nottingham Drive, Suite 130
Baltimore, MD 21236
I Currently *RentOwn
I’m looking to *RefinancePurchaseGet a Construction Loan
State *ConnecticutDelawareDistrict Of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaIndianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganNew HampshireNew JerseyNorth CarolinaPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaTennesseeVirginiaWest Virginia
Name of Preferred OfficerAaron JacobsonAlex JaffeAlex WatersAllan GushueAmanda GarciaAndrew DomshickAnn FlahertyAnn PalrangAnne BorghesaniArlene DeanAyaz RahemanjiAyla HarrisBill McGuireBill Payne, CPABlake PriceBobbie MaurerBrad RestivoBradley FowlerBrandi SharpBrian FossBruce MeyersCaleigh BankerCathy OcharzakChase CusackChris EdgeChris HareChris LoughlinChris SittigChristina OcharzakCourtney FickenCylda HodoDan TinninDarren RickwoodDavid StarleperDavid ToaffDerick AndradeDonny McCordDrew GilmartinEric CaudillEric ShortErin JohnsonGabe TuvekGary PierpontHaley HoytHarry ManleyHeather DevotoIngrid RapavyJack HinderJake RyonJamison MullenJason NaderJason SwansonJay FranklinJeff HalbertJeff StemplerJen WelchJessica EnfingerJim GullaceJim MoranJohn BlatchleyJohn DolbecJordan EngKader SissokoKari StoryKatty IngaKevin WalshKris ShentonLaura ReeseLewis WallerLicela Rojas de BarrigaMarc CiagneMark AskewMark EigenbrodeMarshall FeldmanMarty WallaceMatt MillerMatt NaderMatt ReillyMatthew BorgersonMichael BaschMichelle GreenwaltMike ArcherMike NadeauMike TaylorNancy Cooksey-HoegNicolas MatsangakisOlu AjayiPatrick ParragaRick KuhblankRob MercerRob SchurrRonetta SykesRyan AngierRyan KurrleRyan PaquinSantana BrownScott BetleyScott StoryScott Van StoneSean PierpontShane GuntherSteve HarperTammi LewisTaylor GladuThomas BowenTim MilauskasTim SissonTim WhittierTodd PedeTom CumpstonTom DraperTony LeightyTony OlmertTony PandolfoTracy Cohee HodgesTroy SwigerVictor SalmonWes WilkesWill Camacho
Submit
Welcome to the Borrower Portal! This is your access point to get pre-qualified, send/receive documents, and eSign Disclosures.
Click ‘Access Borrower Portal’ below if you are:
Logging in to an existing account to continue with your pre-qualification.
Logging in to an existing account to send/receive documents, or eSign Disclosures.
Logging in to complete the email verification process.
Click ‘Find a Loan Officer’ below if you are:
Creating a new account to get pre-qualified
Signing into an existing account to get pre-qualified
Once on the desired Loan Officer’s page, click ‘Get Pre-Qualified’ to begin.
Access Borrower Portal
Find a Loan Officer
